Forget swiping on Tinder.
In some Native American
tribes, if a guy
wanted to take you
on a date, he
literally threw a giant
blanket over your head
in the middle of
the street.
It was called blanket
courting.
If a man got
permission from the elders,
he would approach the
woman he liked while
she was out in
the village.
Then, in a massive
public gesture, he would
wrap his large woven
blanket completely around both
of them.
This created a tiny
pitch black, private tent
right in the middle
of the crowded village
so they could whisper
to each other.
Honestly, in a world
without privacy, it's actually
incredibly sweet.
Best of all, everyone
in the village would
completely ignore the giant
walking fabric lump out
of respect.
If you don't believe
me, click the link
in the description to
read the actual research
behind this.